### Summary

Software engineer with around a decade of experience building clean software for a wide range of businesses ranging from Augmented Reality to Financial Services. Possess a strong technical background with a Masters Degree in Computer Engineering from the University of Florida. Lots of experience working in agile teams and also some independently as the only developer. Available for contract work on iOS (Swift / C++), AWS Serverless (Node.js) and Machine Learning projects.

### **Recent Projects**

Moneyou Go	iOS / Android
Modern online mobile banking solution in NL and DE	March 2018 - December 2018
2dehands.be  Largest Online Marketplace in Belgium	iOS June 2016 - December 2017
Blippar Visual Object Recognition and Augmented Reality	iOS June 2015 - May 2016
• Layar World's first major Augmented Reality Platform	iOS November 2014 - May 2016
• Jumbo • E-commerce app for Jumbo Supermarket	iOS February 2014 - November 2014

# Recent Work Experience

### Rabobank (Financial Services)

Senior Mobile Engineer - Freelance

Utrecht, The Netherlands

March 2019 - May 2019

- Briefly joined the native mobile team at Rabobank and helped them with their hybrid app releases.
- Helped in interviewing new iOS Candidates
- Contributed to discussions about Banking IT architecture

# Moneyou / ABN AMRO (Financial Services)

Amsterdam, The Netherlands March 2018 - December 2018

Senior Mobile Engineer - Freelance

- Part of mobile team doing iOS and Android feature development and releases
- Interview new iOS Candidates
- Won moneyou hackathon and successfully implemented suggested features in the app
- Part of team creating a new and compliant banking backend infrastructure with AWS Serverless Lambdas

#### Markplaats / Ebay Inc. (Classifieds)

Senior iOS Engineer - Freelance

Amsterdam, The Netherlands June 2016 - December 2017

- Singlehandedly maintain the 2dehands.be App for Belgium serving millions of users
- Part of the ebay global mobile team building classified apps for 11 different countries for example Gumtree UK
- Setup all required processes such as Automated Testing, Continuous Integration, Crash Analysis etc.
- Successfully hired and trained replacement for the role before exit

### Previous Work Experience

Layar / Blippar (Augmented Reality)

Amsterdam, The Netherlands November 2014 - May 2016

Senior iOS Engineer

- Lead Developer for the iOS Layar App that makes millions of users see Augmented Reality
- Lead Developer for the iOS Layar SDK that help businesses make Augmented Reality solutions
- Part of the team building the Blippar App for visual search
- Contributed to several C++ cross platform projects

## IceMobile Agency (Digital Agency)

Amsterdam, The Netherlands

Senior iOS Engineer

February 2014 - November 2014

- Senior developer in the iOS development team building apps for the leading supermarkets in the Netherlands such as Jumbo and Albert Heijn
- Gathering business requirements and coming up with efficient technical solutions to address them
- Automating user interface testing and setting up continuous integration

### Ebuddy (Chat) iOS Developer

Amsterdam, The Netherlands

June 2013 - January 2014

- Working in the iOS development team building the messaging app XMS that had millions of users around the world and was a competitor to watsapp

### MicroStrategy Inc. (Business Intelligence)

McLean, VA

Software Engineer

September 2010 - January 2012

- Worked on several iOS development projects for the clients of Microstrategy and helped automate various tasks. Also helped develop the microstrategy SDK, iOS was a pretty new technology at this point so this was some really good experience.

# Citisync (Event Management)

Gainesville,FL

iOS Developer

January 2010- July 2010

- Singlehandedly built the citisync iOS Application. This was when iOS 3 was the latest version. Also my first experience as an iOS Developer and it piqued my interest in the field

#### Bloomberg LP (Financial Services)

New York, NY

Financial Software Development Intern

May 2009 - August 2009

- As an intern in the manhattan office, I helped out with a number of projects in the Global Trading team writing code in C++ and managing large mainframe supercomputers

#### Education

### University of Florida

Gainesville,FL

Masters in Computer Engineering

August 2008 - August 2010

- CGPA: 3.6/4.0

#### Skills

Languages: Swift, Objective C, C, C++, Python, Bash, Javascript(Node.js)

Technical Skills: iOS, Serverless, Machine Learning

### Other Interests

Pilot Training, Crossfit, Salsa, Travel, Pool and Snooker